<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; The Landing Pad</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/admin/feed/?simply_static_page=216" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 05:07:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.6</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Representative of the Bahrain Economic Development Board</title>
		<link>/2017/11/representative-of-the-bahrain-economic-development-board/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the Hong Kong representative of this public agency, we are responsible for establishing and developing strategic investor relationships to facilitate foreign direct investment from Hong Kong into Bahrain across [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the Hong Kong representative of this public agency, we are responsible for establishing and developing strategic investor relationships to facilitate foreign direct investment from Hong Kong into Bahrain across key industry sectors.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business development visit programme</title>
		<link>/2017/11/business-development-visit-programme/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We arranged a professional visit programme for a client based in the UK looking to meet with potential clients here in Hong Kong, with a view to ascertaining local business [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We arranged a professional visit programme for a client based in the UK looking to meet with potential clients here in Hong Kong, with a view to ascertaining local business opportunities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Government relations advisory and stakeholder management</title>
		<link>/2017/11/government-relations-advisory-and-stakeholder-management/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Provision of advice and strategic relationship management with the HKSARG on a high profile public land use project in Hong Kong. Prior to this role was heavily involved in content [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Provision of advice and strategic relationship management with the HKSARG on a high profile public land use project in Hong Kong. Prior to this role was heavily involved in content generation and drafting of the winning tender for the project.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European precious metal association industry outreach</title>
		<link>/2017/11/european-precious-metal-association-industry-outreach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1257</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Engaged to deliver a report derived from in-person interviews with senior managers in the jewellery manufacturing, wholesale and retail industry in Southern China that would inform near-future demand, as well [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Engaged to deliver a report derived from in-person interviews with senior managers in the jewellery manufacturing, wholesale and retail industry in Southern China that would inform near-future demand, as well as acceptable price points, of the precious metal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Representative of International Health Industries, State Government of Victoria</title>
		<link>/2017/11/representative-of-international-health-industries-state-government-of-victoria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the Greater China representative based in Hong Kong, we were responsible for trade and investment lead generation and project delivery in the areas of healthcare services, related product manufacturing [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the Greater China representative based in Hong Kong, we were responsible for trade and investment lead generation and project delivery in the areas of healthcare services, related product manufacturing and distribution, and healthcare technology and innovation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enterprise Mauritius in Hong Kong</title>
		<link>/2017/11/enterprise-mauritius-in-hong-kong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We organised a mini-trade show, with more than 100 confirmed meetings across two days, for agri-producers from Mauritius seeking to connect with local wholesalers and distributors in Hong Kong. Products [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We organised a mini-trade show, with more than 100 confirmed meetings across two days, for agri-producers from Mauritius seeking to connect with local wholesalers and distributors in Hong Kong. Products included fresh cut flowers, seafood, sugar, and teas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
